delta[r] is last layer

Then compute from k = r-1 to 1, so from second to last layer

Compute delta[k], overlapping subproblems, dynamic programming so cache our results 

Need to consider all possible path for loss function  but this time is dong it backwards

W come from, previous ways and derivative of z

Can use bumpy to compute this

How can this be more generalised so its more software engineering to find circuits. A driver to make deep learning. 

Allow us to prototype more quickly 

